### **VERONIKA SAVLUK**

JUNIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER



### **CONTACTS**

Kyiv, Ukraine +38(066) 195-42-12 s veronica@ukr.net GitHub <u>Linkedin</u>

## **TECH SKILLS**

HTML5 CSS3 Java Script React Redux Styled Components **REST API** GitHub **VSCode** Trello etc.

### **SOFT SKILLS**

Ability to work efficiently both individually and in a team Critical and analytical thinking Organizational skills Quick learning skills Risk Taking

#### **LANGUAGES**

English: intermediate Ukrainian: native Russian: native

#### **SUMMARY**

If you have to start from the beginning, then start with what you really like.

I am a Full Stack Developer with practical experience in JavaScript, React, Redux, Node.js, HTML and CSS3 and 13 years in the banking sector as a Risk Manager.

If you wish to have reliable person who values time and likes to help other then I am waiting for your feedback.

#### **PROJECTS**

### Induvidual projects:

- Phonebook is the application for saving contacts: React, Redux Toolkit, react-routerdom, react-loader-spinner, HTML5, CSS3, axios, Formik, yup, Chakra-ui/react [sourse code repository];
- WebStudio is the landing page with adaptive layouts design: HTML5, CSS3 (Sass), metodology BEM, Prettier, squoosh, Icomoon, svgomg [sourse code repository];
- Filmoteka is the application for searching movie information: React (hooks, react-icons, styled-components, HTML5, CSS3, axios, prop-types [source code repository].

### Team projects:

- Petly is the application for searching information about pets and services with the possibility of maintaining your own account and add your favorite pets. I was team lead of frontend and created some components for the "Find pet" page: Node.js, Express, CORS, multer, React, Redux-toolkit, bcrypt.js, Cloudinary, MongoDB, mongoose, Gravatar, Joi, Swagger-ui-express, react-router-dom, nanoid, react-icons, react-toastify, react-loader-spinner, axios, Formik, yup, @emotion/styled [sourse code repository];
- IceCream is the landing page with adaptive layouts design for ice-cream store. I was working with section-hero: HTML5, CSS3 (Sass), metodology BEM, Prettier, validator Nu Html Checker, squoosh, Icomoon, svgomg [sourse code repostory];
- **Filmoteka** is the application for searching a movie and formation of own movies library. I was coding main-container and my-library-container, render watched movies: JS, HTML5, CSS3, tui-pagination, api.themoviedb.org [sourse code repository].

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Leading Asset Management Economist**

May 2017 - October 2021

- developed asset management plans for 12 insolvent banks;
- improvement of management reporting;
- development of financial models etc.

### **Deputy Head of Credit Sales**

March 2016 - May 2017

- support sale of loans;
- · development of financial models and methodology etc.

#### Risk Manager

IT school GoIT

**PJS Artem-bank** 

Kyiv

July 2008 - March 2016

- management reporting (P&I,Cash Flow, Balance sheet etc.);
- setting limits and monitoring;
- development of methodology etc.

# **EDUCATION**

Fullstack developer February 2022 - February 2023

**International University of Financy** Financy September 2004 - June 2009